pianoworld.com 2006-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Piano World

[](http://www.pianoworld.com/)SM

**Browse Piano World**  
(Choose from drop-down and click GO)   
Or see our [Directory/Site Map](http://www.pianoworld.com/directory.htm)

[In PianoSupplies.com now](http://www.pianosupplies.com/Merchant2/merchant.mvc?Screen=SFNT) Our online store   
Piano tuning tools, piano lamps, cushions, benches, metronomes, moving equipment, and other accessories. 

In a hurry? **  
(from MusicNotes.com) or order a copy shipped to you.   
It's great! You can listen to what the music should sound like, and even watch the notes being played! 

Add an [RSS Feed](http://www.pianoworld.com/rss.htm) of our **World Famous Piano Forums** to your [   
My Yahoo!](http://www.pianoworld.com/rss.htm)   
account, or to your own web site! 

**Top**

  |   

Privacy Policy - Piano World 

| 

> Privacy Policy for:   
>  Piano World, PianoSupplies.com and PianoHelp.com 
> 
> * * *
> 
> PianoWorld.com, PianoSupplies.com,and PianoHelp.com adhere to the same privacy policy.   
> Any reference to Piano World below applies to all three Web sites. 
> 
> Your Privacy 
> 
> At Piano World, we are committed to protecting your privacy. This policy also applies to non U.S. residence. We use the information we collect about you to process orders, post your ads and to provide better service. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. 
> 
> What information do we collect? How do we use it? 
> 
>   * When you **enter a contest** or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. 
>   * If you **place an ad** with us, we may additionally ask for your phone number, however you will have the option of requesting that we do not post your phone number in your ad. We do not recommend posting your address unless it is a business ad. 
>   * When you **place an order** , we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order. Any credit card or check information is strictly for the use of the processing companies that handle this part of the transactions for us. We do not keep any credit card or check data on our own computers and we never share this information with anyone else. 
>   * We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. We will not abuse this privilege. These announcements currently only go out about 2 or 3 times a year. If you never want to receive any announcements or special offers from us, send a e-mail message to [webmaster@pianoworld.com](mailto:webmaster@pianoworld.com?Subject=No%20Emails%20from%20Piano%20World) . (If you use more than one e-mail account with Piano World, send this message from each e-mail account you use.) 
>   * If you would like to keep up with what is happening in the piano industry and on the Piano World Web sites... **To receive our FREE Piano Newsletters** Join our world famous [Piano Forums](http://www.pianoworld.com/ubb/ubb/ultimatebb.php) today (they are free too) and automatically receive our free newsletters too. 
> 

> 
> How does Piano World protect customer information? 
> 
> When you place orders or submit one of our forms, we use a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. 
> 
> What about "cookies"? 
> 
> "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. They allow companies to offer special features (like ™Amazon.com's 1-Click(sm) shopping). We use cookies to track your sale as you progress through our store and to assign you a "customer ID". The customer ID is only to make it easier to shop with us in the future. The next time you shop with PianoSupplies.com, you only need to enter your ID in the Ship To / Bill To screen and it will automatically fill in your information for you (we do not retain your credit information). 
> 
> Will Piano World disclose the information it collects to outside parties? 
> 
> Piano World does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Piano World may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. 
> 
> In summary 
> 
> We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site(s) to make shopping at PianoWorld.com & PianoSupplies.com possible, to post your ad(s) and to enhance your overall experience with us. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. 
> 
> Your consent 
> 
> By using our Web site(s), you consent to the collection and use of this information by Piano World. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 
> 
> Questions or comments? 
> 
> If you have any questions or comments about our policies, please feel free to Contact us. 
> 
> Purchase Policy 
> 
> For information about making purchases in our store, PianoSupplies.com, please visit [PianoSupplies.com](http://www.pianosupplies.com/)
> 
> Right to know 
> 
> If you would like a copy of the information Piano World has on file about you, send an s.a.s.e. along with your name, address and phone number to:   
>  Privacy   
>  Piano World   
>  38 Parky Drive   
>  Enfield, CT 06082 
> 
> We will only send this information to the name and address contained in the information we collected.   
> If you feel that there are any inaccuracies in this information, write back to us and we will correct it. Please note that this information is exactly as we received it from you. 
> 
> < Back.   
  
---
